VAGUE PROMPT  →  CLEAR BRIEF
AI STARTS TOO FAST.
WITH AN INCOMPLETE PROMPT.
LUMIXIA ADDS
AN ALIGNMENT STEP.
BUILT WITH CODEX + GPT-5.6
BUILT DURING OPENAI BUILD WEEK
WITH CODEX + GPT-5.6
ONE VAGUE SENTENCE.
GOOGLE SIGN-IN
PLUS REQUIRED MFA
ADAPTIVE INTERVIEW
ONE FOCUSED QUESTION AT A TIME.
NOTHING RUNS WHILE YOU TYPE.
ON SUBMIT: GPT-5.6 SOL
RUNS THROUGH CODEX
FACTS · ASSUMPTIONS · CONTRADICTIONS
THEN THE NEXT BEST QUESTION
8D CONFIDENCE
THE SERVER SCORES
NOT THE MODEL
8 DIMENSIONS
FROM PROBLEM TO SUCCESS
ONE ANSWER CLARIFIES
PROBLEM + AUDIENCE
0%  →  38% CONFIDENCE
+59 ALIGNMENT
FIVE ADAPTIVE TURNS
33%  →  92% ALIGNMENT
GOALS · DELIVERABLES · NON-GOALS
CONSTRAINTS · RISKS · ASSUMPTIONS
OPEN QUESTIONS · NEXT STEPS
EVERY CLAIM HAS EVIDENCE
HUMAN APPROVAL
REVISE ANY SECTION
ONLY APPROVED SNAPSHOTS LEAVE
EDITING CREATES
A NEW REVISION
IDEMPOTENT NOTION SYNC
NOTION GETS APPROVED ONLY
SAFE TO RETRY
SAME PAGE. NO DUPLICATES.
CODEX BUILD EVIDENCE
CODEX SCAFFOLDED
BUILT · TESTED · HARDENED
MILESTONES · PRS · CI
CODEX SESSION EVIDENCE
NO PROMPTS. NO PERSONAL DATA.
GPT-5.6 SOL  ·  NO API KEY
GPT-5.6 SOL
THROUGH MY CODEX PLAN
FROM AMBIGUITY
TO A HUMAN-APPROVED HANDOFF